<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Training on Ketch Networking</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Training on Ketch Networking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Optical LAN Training: Network Planning &amp; Design</title>
      <link>/services/olan_npd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/olan_npd/</guid>
      <description>Do you need to plan and design Tellabs Optical LAN solutions?
This course is for network engineers who are, or will be, responsible for designing and planning networks with Tellabs Optical LAN. The curriculum is appropriate for Network Architects, Network Design Consultants and Technical Sales Staff
Class Specifics Course Duration: 3 days
Class Location: Live Classroom, On-Site or Virtual Classroom
Class Size: Up to 8 Students
Day 1 – Optical LAN System Architecture and Applications Overview</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optical LAN Training: Operations, Provisioning &amp; Maintenance and Advanced Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>/services/olan_opmadv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/olan_opmadv/</guid>
      <description>Do you operate a mission critical highly secure, high availability Tellabs Optical LAN?
This course is designed for Network Operations and/or any individuals responsible for operating, provisioning, maintaining and monitoring a Tellabs Optical LAN system. This course is also intended for employees responsible for the administration, installation, testing, maintenance or technical support of the Optical LAN.
Prerequisites
Basic knowledge in Ethernet switching and routing; including VLAN concepts, IP/subnetting, basic QoS knowledge and the basic concepts of port security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optical LAN Training: Deployment Certification</title>
      <link>/services/olan_cdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/olan_cdc/</guid>
      <description>Are you a Tellabs OLAN Reseller that needs to certify installations?
This course is designed for Network Operations and/or any individuals responsible for installing, operating, provisioning, maintaining and monitoring a Tellabs Optical LAN system. The curriculum is specifically designed for the following roles who have little to no prior experience installing, turning up, operating and provisioning a Tellabs Optical LAN system.
This course must be conducted at Tellabs facility in Dallas, TX or suitable lab environment to support extensive hands on activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optical LAN Training: Operations, Provisioning &amp; Maintenance</title>
      <link>/services/olan_opm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/olan_opm/</guid>
      <description>Will you be responsible for Provisioning and Maintaining a Tellabs Optical LAN?
This course is designed for Network Operations and/or any individuals responsible for operating, provisioning, maintaining and monitoring a Tellabs Optical LAN. This course is also intended for employees responsible for the administration, installation, testing, maintenance or technical support of the Optical LAN.
Prerequisites
Basic knowledge in Ethernet switching and routing; including VLAN concepts, IP/subnetting, basic QoS knowledge and the basic concepts of port security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tellabs 1000 MSAP: Operations, Provisioning &amp; Maintenance</title>
      <link>/services/t1000_opm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/t1000_opm/</guid>
      <description> Are a Service Provider who needs training for Tellabs 1000 MSAP in your Access Network?
We provide the Tellabs Operations, Provisioning &amp;amp; Maintenance Course and custom training for the Tellabs 1000 MSAP.
Please submit form to register for this course: Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>